move away that's where the key is moving away e
отодвинь вот та Где ключ отодвигая е
pushing away I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky where are you from
отодвигая я из города Хмельницкий ты
From the city of St. Petersburg conscript
откуда Из города
no
срочник нет
cadet for whom
курсант на кого
cadet for operator of units and
курсанти на эксплуататор подразделений и
wired communication systems in short
систем проводной связи короче
signalman Yes they say that they will die
связист Да говорят что дохнут
first, something's not sure about that Well, that's what it
первыми что-то не уверен в этом Ну это
seems to me Well  the guys
как мне кажется Ну мне ребята
told me about these Because I told them they are
рассказывали эти Потому что я говорил их
allowed to lay communications km ass Well,
пускают прокладывать связь км [__] Ну
these are radio operators and I’m a little different, I
это радисты а я чуть-чуть другой я это
understand this more with computers and machines,
больше с компьютерами и машинами понял
you’re a
ты
computer scientist, well, you can say so, but what do
компьютерщик ну можно и так сказать а
you fumble around in computers,
шаришь по й
cadets need to study, yes  Well,
регу курсантам надо учиться да Ну я
as a matter of fact, I’m still only in my first year. And what kind of
собственно говоря ещ первый год только А
box is there? There’s a
что там за ящик какой-то на шкафу
suitcase like that on the
чемодан такой
closet. We have an office, in the sense of an office. What is an office? An office is where the laptops are. And we work purely with papers,
где стоят ноуты А мы чисто с бумажками
but why the hell do
работаем а нахрен
n’t we touch Naka?  there's a corpse
Нака не трогаем так [__] может там труп
lying in a suitcase, and okay, damn, why are you
лежит в чемодане да и ладно [__] Вы что
driving me stupid, even we have two
гоните тупа у нас даже у нас и два
suitcases like that, two corpses. Maybe there are two
чемодана таких два трупа Может там два
previous cadets lying there. Yes, okay,
курсанта предыдущих лежат Да нормально
we're next, no damn, I really wonder
мы следующий не блин реально интересно
what's in the suitcase. Well, it's empty, we opened it,
что в чемодане Ну там пусто мы открывали
well, show me  I don’t believe you’re driving away You
та ну покажи я не верю ты гонишь Ты же
said that they came, he was standing Show me what’s in
сказал что пришли он стоял Покажи что в
the suitcase Take off the suitcase
чемодане Сними чемодан
Maybe Putin [ __ ] in there
Может там Путин
[ __ ] how it opens you see you
насрал бля как открывается видишь ты его
didn’t open it you say it’s
не открывал говоришь
empty Well I at least lift it with one hand
пустой Ну я его одной рукой как минимум
there can’t be
поднимаю там не может быть
anyone there secret documents For example
никого секретные документы Например
there could
может
be a suitcase
быть чемодан
open Well, you can’t open the
открыть Ну что не можешь открыть чемодан
suitcase, move these things aside, the key is where the key is,
отодвинь вот эти штучки ключ та Где ключ
pushing it away, pushing it to the side, it doesn’t
отодвигая его отодвигая в бок он не
move, but it moves, you see what I’m rummaging in. In
двигается а двигается видишь ты что я
short, I open the
шарю Короче я дистанционно открываю
suitcases remotely, you see Op, come on and the second one is
чемоданы видишь Оп давай и второй
also unpacking the cadet’s suitcase, you
также распаковка чемодана курсантской ты
Take it off and on the ground  Open it now,
Сними его и на земле Открой сейчас
it’ll fall out on you, it’ll
выпадет на тебя нахрен выпадет оно
all fall out, and you said nothing, and what the [ __ ] is
всё а ты говорил пустой а что там бля аж
there, it’s really interesting, there are some secret documents, what’s in there, this is a scam,
интересно там какие-то тайные документы
what else are showings, it’s [ __ ]
там вот это развод что ещё показы бля аж
interesting, someone is keeping this rubbish
интересно это кто-то этот хлам держит
there, the pioneers, what’s this about you?  there’s some
там пионеры че это у вас походу какой-то
kid in a ka wanker in a suitcase with a
дет в ка [__] есть в чемодане с
cool PTO Dava
прикольной ВОМ Дава
was that a folder or what is it And this is
это папка была или что что это А это
just plywood and I’m throwing everything in it’s already
просто фанерка да всё закидываю аж
interesting in the second suitcase there’s also something
интересно во втором чемодане тоже что-то
maybe some kind of hiding place [ __ ] really
может быть какой-то тайник бля аж
interesting Dude you’re really cool
интересный Чувак ты реально прикольный
Class It's cool, it's not really a cool suitcase,
Класс Прикольно не реально чемодан
such a leopard Yes, throw
классный такой леопард Да закинь
it in, let's unpack the second suitcase, it
его давай ещё второй чемодан распакуем
became really interesting, damn I never thought
аж интересно стало блин никогда не думал
that such suitcases
что такие чемоданы меня
would interest me, this is heavy. By the way, it's heavy, something might be
тяжёлый о там что-то может быть
interesting there. There ngr ngr you've already
интересно Там нгр нгр ты уже
watched Think about it there  grenade now
смотрел Прикинь там граната сейчас
F1 [ __ ] And this is also locked with a key Yes, no, there are no
F1 бляд А это тоже на ключ закры Да нет
keys,
тни ключей
no freezing, no freezing, show what
не зависая не зависая показывай че
Damn, we still didn’t find out what was in the suitcase, what was
Блин мы так и не узнали что в чемодане
in this suitcase, damn it’s a
что было в этом чемодане блин это
mystery, it will go away with this kid Or maybe it
загадка уйдёт с этим пацаном А може он
exploded like an fpv drone Yes  maybe like fpv
взорвался как fpv Дрон Да може как fpv
Drone but doesn’t show at the
Дрон но не показывает в
end kapets
конце капец
female there was a stretcher that in the black
самка там была растяжка что в чёрном
suitcase our letter is on my Telegram directly at the same
чемодане нащи пись на мий Telegram прямо
time axis VN
зараз ось ВН
apok tse more and more
апок це дуже и дуже
important Ne
важ Ne